<resources>
    <string name="text_terms_1" translatable="false">"Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile - Terms of Use

Last Revised: January 31, 2020

Orbs Ltd. (“Orbs”, “we”, “our”) welcomes you (“User(s)” or “you”) to the Beta version of the My Orbs Wallet service (the “App”). You may use the App in accordance with the terms and conditions set forth herein.

1. Acceptance of the Terms

By downloading, entering, connecting to, accessing or using the App, and/or by installing and/or providing permission to the App through your device or account, you acknowledge that you have read and understood the following terms of use and you agree to be bound by them and to comply with all applicable laws and regulations regarding your use of the App and you acknowledge that these Terms constitute a binding and enforceable legal contract between Orbs and you.
IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, PLEASE DO NOT ENTER, CONNECT TO, ACCESS OR USE THE APP IN ANY MANNER, DO NOT INSTALL OR PROVIDE PERMISSIONS WITH RESPECT TO THE APP AND/OR PROMPTLY UNINSTALL THE APP AND/OR PROMPTLY REMOVE THE APP PERMISSIONS FROM YOUR ACCOUNT AND DEVICE.
The App is available only to individuals who (a) are at least eighteen (18) years old (see Section 22 below); and (b) possess the legal authority to enter into these Terms and to form a binding agreement under any applicable law.

2. The App

The App is a Beta version of a non-custodial application designed by Orbs that can be used to manage your holdings of ORBS blockchain tokens (the “Orbs Tokens”) that are usable on the Orbs blockchain network, a next-generation blockchain infrastructure (the “Orbs Network”), and to participate in the Orbs Universe proof-of-stake ecosystem, which allows holders of Orbs Tokens to participate in the operation, security and governance of the Orbs Network by staking or delegating Orbs Tokens (the “Orbs Proof-of-Stake Universe”). More information about the Orbs Proof-of-Stake Ecosystem is available here: https://www.orbs.com/orbs-universe/. The App may enable Users to access the following services (collectively, the “Services”):
2.1. To transfer information and content between the Users and blockchain infrastructure provided by the Orbs Network or the Ethereum blockchain, as applicable;
2.2. To open and maintain a personal non-custodial wallet (“Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile”) that will be associated with such User’s Underlying Account with the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet or Ledger hardware wallet(such terms as defined below);
2.3. Through the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile, facilitate storage and monitoring of Orbs Tokens by Users;
2.4. Through the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile, participate in the Orbs Proof-of-Stake Ecosystem by staking or delegating tokens; or
2.5. Use such other services made available by Orbs through the App from time to time.
The App and any website hosting, or used to access, the App may also provide information regarding Orbs, including content, contact information, videos, text, logos, button icons, images, data compilations, links, other specialized content, documentation, data, related graphics, and other features obtained from or through the App (collectively, the “Content”).

3. Account Registration

In order to use the App, you must download the App to your device. By downloading the App, you provide the App with applicable permissions to read certain information and take certain actions on your device, your account with the associated Google Play Store, Samsung Galaxy Store and the Samsung Blockchain Keystore, which may in turn interact with the Samsung Blockchain Wallet (collectively, the “Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet”) or Ledger HW Wallet (the “Underlying Accounts”).
The App is connected to, derives information from and allows you to engage in certain activities within, your Underlying Accounts, which are password protected. In order to protect the security of your Underlying Account and the personal information used by the App to the greatest extent possible, you must safeguard and not disclose the log-in details of your Underlying Accounts and must supervise the use of such Underlying Accounts. You are fully and solely responsible for the security of your Underlying Accounts and all activity on your Underlying Accounts and on the App, even if such activities were not committed by you. Your Underlying Accounts are essential for utilizing the App, and your loss of your device or the password or other credentials needed to access your Underlying Accounts may cause you to be unable to access the App. Use of the App via your device or your Underlying Accounts by any person will enable such person to use the App to interact with your underlying Accounts and take unauthorized actions therein.
Orbs hereby reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to restrict any User from using the App at any time, for any reason, including but not limited to claims by a third party that actions taken by such User violates certain rights of such third parties.
If you wish to remove the App, you can uninstall the App from your device. From that date you will no longer be able to utilize the App (see further details with respect thereto in the Privacy Policy, as defined below).
DELETING THE APP MAY CAUSE THE LOSS OF ANY ORBS TOKEN HELD IN YOUR ORBS POS WALLET FOR MOBILE AND MAY CAUSE THE LOSS OF CERTAIN INFORMATION YOU PROVIDED US AND/OR THE CAPACITY OF YOUR ACCOUNT. WE DO NOT ACCEPT ANY LIABILITY FOR SUCH LOSS.

4. Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile

The App connects to the Ethereum blockchain, where Orbs Tokens reside, through the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet. The Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet allows you to purchase, store, and engage in transactions using Ethereum cryptocurrency and other blockchain tokens based on the Ethereum protocol and other blockchain protocols, including the Orbs Tokens. You will not be able to engage in any activity in the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile other than through the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet and Ledger HW wallet. The Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile will only recognize you as a user and you will only be able to interact with the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile if the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet is connected to your device and unlocked. There is no other way to sign up or to interact directly with the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile.
Public Nature of Transactions: Transactions that take place through the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile are ultimately managed and confirmed via the Ethereum blockchain. You understand that your Ethereum public address will be made publicly visible whenever you engage in a transaction through the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile.
Non-Custodial Wallet: The Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile is not a "web wallet". You do not create an account or give us your funds to hold onto. No data leaves your computer, your device or your browser. At no point will Orbs ever take custody of Orbs Tokens through the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile. We make it easy for you to create, save, and access your information and interact with the Orbs Network and the Orbs Proof-of-Stake Ecosystem. You acknowledge that Orbs is not responsible for transferring, safeguarding, or maintaining your private keys or any digital currency associated therewith. If you lose or mishandle associated digital currency private keys, or if such digital currency private keys are stolen from you, you acknowledge that you may not be able to recover associated digital currency, and that Orbs is not responsible for such loss. You acknowledge that Orbs is not responsible for any loss, damage or liability arising from your failure to comply with the terms hereunder.
The Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile software allows you to stake or delegate Orbs Tokens via the Ethereum blockchain and the Orbs Network by utilizing information, such as SeedHash and your wallet address information, that is generated by the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet based on cryptographic private and public key pairs that are associated with and stored within your Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet account. YOU MUST STORE, OUTSIDE OF THE SERVICES, A BACKUP OF ALL SUCH CREDENTIALS, INCLUDING YOUR PASSPHRASES, IDENTIFIERS, BACKUP PHRASES, PRIVATE KEYS AND NETWORK ADDRESSES. If you do not maintain a backup of your data that is held outside of the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile, you may not be able to access Orbs Tokens previously accessed using your Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile in the event that we discontinue or no longer offer some or all of the services provided through the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile or may otherwise lose access to Orbs Tokens. We are not responsible for maintaining this data on your behalf.
YOUR PRIVATE KEYS WILL REMAIN IN YOUR POSSESSION AND THEIR SECURITY IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY ? ALWAYS BACKUP YOUR KEYS.
Dependence on Third Party Applications: The Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile connects to the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet, which provides a platform for managing accounts on the Ethereum blockchain, through a website and browser plugin. By connecting through the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet, the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile is able to effectuate staking, delegation to Guardians and other actions with respect to your Orbs Tokens. If you do not log on to the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile with the correct device and/or if the device does not have the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet installed or activated, you will be recognized by the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile and you will not be able to interact with the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile in any way.
The Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet is a third party application that is not under the control of Orbs. Orbs does not own and does not control Samsung or any of the following third-party products used for the function of the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile: the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet, the Ethereum blockchain or any other third-party site, product, service or infrastructure that you may choose to access, visit, or use for the purpose of interacting with or using the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile. Accordingly, by using the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile, you acknowledge that Orbs has no control over, and no duty to take any action regarding, any transaction engaged in through the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet’s, or any other third party’s, functionality. Orbs will not be held liable, and are not liable, for the acts or omissions by Samsung or any other third party, nor are we liable, or will we be held liable, for any damage that you may suffer as a result of interacting with or using any of the mentioned or unmentioned third parties. You are solely responsible for the safety and security of your Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet and/or any other service you utilize to interact with the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile or the Orbs Network.
You should review the terms of use and privacy policy of the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure and Ledger HW wallet, which can be viewed on your device explorer at: [Samsung Blockchain Wallet - Settings - Samsung Block Keystore - About Blockchain Keystore - Terms and Conditions] and [Samsung Blockchain Wallet - Settings - Samsung Block Keystore - About Blockchain Keystore - Privacy Policy] and https://shop.ledger.com/pages/privacy-policy, respectively.
You are solely responsible for the safety and security of your use of the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile.
Risk Disclosures Relating to the Orbs POS Mobile Wallet. By utilizing the Services or interacting with the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile, the Orbs Network or the Orbs Proof-of-Stake Ecosystem in any way, you represent that you understand the inherent risks associated with cryptographic systems; and warrant that you have an understanding of the usage and intricacies of native cryptographic tokens, like the Orbs Tokens, Ether (ETH) and Bitcoin (BTC), smart contract based tokens such as those that follow the Ethereum Token Standard, and blockchain-based software systems, including, but not limited to, the following risks:

A. In order to be completed, any transaction created with the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile, which may include, without limitation, a delegation or staking of Orbs Tokens or any other form of participation in the Orbs Proof-of-Stake Ecosystem, must be confirmed and recorded on the Ethereum blockchain and the Orbs Network. Such networks are decentralized, peer-to-peer networks operated by independent third parties, which are not owned, controlled or operated by Orbs.
B. Orbs does not control the actions of Guardians and Validators on the Orbs Network or nodes on the Ethereum blockchain and therefore cannot and does not ensure that any transaction details you submit via the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile will be confirmed on the relevant networks. The transaction details you submit via the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile may not be completed, or may be substantially delayed, by one or both of the applicable networks used to process the transaction. We do not guarantee that the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile can transfer title or right in the Orbs Tokens or make any warranties whatsoever with regard to title.
C. Once transaction details have been submitted via the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile, we cannot assist you to cancel or otherwise modify your transaction or transaction details.

No Password Retrieval. With respect to the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile, Orbs does not receive or store any password connected to the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile, nor any keys, network addresses or transaction history. We cannot assist you with the retrieval of any password or credentials you need to utilize the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile. You are solely responsible for remembering, storing and keeping secret your passwords, private keys or any other credentials. Any Orbs Tokens you have associated with the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile may become inaccessible if you do not know or keep secret your password or other credentials associated with the underlying Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet, or if your device is lost or compromised. Any third party with knowledge of one or more of your credentials (including, without limitation, a backup phrase, wallet identifier or password) or access to your device can potentially engage in unauthorized transactions in Orbs Tokens in your wallet.
When you create any blockchain wallet with the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet, which will connect to the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile, you must: (a) create a strong password that you do not use for any other website or online service; (b) provide accurate and truthful information; (c) protect and keep secret all credentials for the wallet; (d) protect access to your device and your wallet; (e) promptly notify Samsung if you discover or otherwise suspect any security breaches related to your wallet; and (f) use any backup functionality provided through the wallet and safeguard your backup files. You agree to take responsibility for all activities that occur with your wallet and accept all risks of any authorized or unauthorized access to your wallet, to the maximum extent permitted by law.
Fees. Orbs does not currently charge a fee for the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile or transactions conducted therein.  However, we reserve the right to do so in the future, and in such case shall display to you any applicable fees prior to you incurring the fee. Network fees (including, without limitation “miner’s fees”) required to use the Orbs Network or the Ethereum blockchain may apply to a transaction. We may attempt to calculate such a fee for you. Our calculation may not be sufficient, or it may be excessive. You may select a greater or lesser fee. You are solely responsible for selecting and paying any such fee and Orbs shall neither advance nor fund such a fee on your behalf, nor be responsible for any excess or insufficient fee calculation.
Be safe &#38; secure: If you elect to utilize the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile or otherwise hold any Orbs Tokens, we highly recommend that you educate yourself on blockchain industry standard recommendations on how to be proactive about your security.
We are not responsible for any loss: The Orbs Network, the Orbs Token, the Ethereum blockchain and the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet are still under active development and as such, (a) may contain bugs, errors and defects, (b) may function improperly or be subject to periods of downtime and unavailability, (c) may result in total or partial loss or corruption of data and (d) may be modified at any time, including through the release of subsequent versions, all with or without notice to you.
While we have thoroughly tested the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile, there is always the possibility something unexpected happens that causes your Orbs Tokens to be lost. Please do not spend more to purchase Orbs Tokens than you are willing to lose, and please be careful."
    </string>
    <string name="text_terms_2" translatable="false">"
5. Orbs Tokens

The Orbs Network is based on blockchain technology. Furthermore, the Orbs Network requires the use of a virtual currency, the Orbs Tokens, for certain aspects of its functionality. Without limitation, the Orbs Tokens are required for application developers to pay transaction fees to validators for providing the services needed to run their applications on the Orbs Network. In addition, participants in the Orbs Proof-of-Stake Ecosystem may utilize the Orbs Tokens in order to participate in the Orbs Proof-of-Stake Ecosystem by direct voting or delegating the vote associated with such Orbs Tokens, and may receive rewards in the form of Orbs Tokens for such activities, all in accordance with the then-applicable security governance and operations model.
Accordingly, when using the App to access the Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile or otherwise interacting with the Orbs Network, you should be aware of the following risks associated with virtual currency, including the Orbs Tokens, and blockchain-based software, including the Orbs Network:
● virtual currency is not legal tender, is not backed by the government, and accounts and value balances are not subject to Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation or Securities Investor Protection Corporation protections or similar laws in any jurisdiction;
● legislative and regulatory changes or actions at the state, federal, or international level may adversely affect the use, transfer, exchange, and value of virtual currency;
● transactions in virtual currency are generally irreversible, and, accordingly, losses due to fraudulent or accidental transactions may not be recoverable;
● some virtual currency transactions shall be deemed to be made when recorded on a “blockchain” ledger, which is not necessarily the date or time that the customer initiates the transaction;
● the value of virtual currency is derived from the continued willingness of market participants to exchange fiat currency for virtual currency, which may result in the potential for permanent and total loss of value of a particular virtual currency should the market for that virtual currency disappear;
● there is no assurance that a person who accepts a virtual currency as payment today will continue to do so in the future;
● the volatility and unpredictability of the price of virtual currency relative to fiat currency may result in significant loss or tax liability over a short period of time;
● the nature of virtual currency may lead to an increased risk of fraud or cyber-attack;
● the nature of virtual currency means that any technological difficulties experienced by You may prevent the access or use of a customer’s virtual currency;
● the Orbs Network is likely to experience scheduled and unscheduled downtime, interruptions, delays, hard forks, bugs, viruses, and cyberattacks;
● the Orbs Network may from time to time lack features or functionality and/or require maintenance, support or other adjustments;
● the Orbs Network rests or relies on open-source software, and there is a risk that a person introduces weaknesses, bugs, viruses or other malicious code into the core infrastructural elements of the Orbs Network causing the system to lose or erase all or a portion of the Orbs Tokens used in connection with the Orbs Network;
● it is possible that the Orbs Network will not be used by a large number of external businesses, individuals, and other organizations and that there will be limited public interest in the creation and development of distributed applications. Such a lack of interest could impact the development of the Orbs Network and potential uses of Orbs Tokens. It is not possible to predict the success of any development efforts of any party;
● the actual existence and performance of the Orbs Network is dependent on the collective actions of various participants in the Orbs Network, including, among others, Validators, Guardians and holders of Orbs Tokens. It is possible that the Orbs Network may not continue to exist and may not perform as expected if such parties cease their activities on the Orbs Network. No one, including Orbs, can guarantee that such parties will continue to act or that the Orbs Network will continue exist or perform at the expected level;
● you recognize that the Orbs Network is under development and may undergo significant changes over time and you acknowledge that any expectations regarding the form and functionality of the Orbs Network held by you may not be met upon release of the Orbs Network or any update thereto, for any number of reasons including a change in the design and implementation plans and execution of the implementation of the Orbs Network;
● the state of cryptocurrency can advance over time and advances in code cracking, or technical advances such as the development of quantum computers, could present risks to the Orbs Tokens and the Orbs Network, which could result in the theft or loss of Orbs Tokens. To the extent possible, participants in the Orbs Network may attempt to update the protocol underlying the Orbs Network to account for any advances in cryptography and to incorporate additional security measures, but the future of cryptography cannot be predicted and there can be no guarantee that any security updates will be made in a timely or successful manner;
● as with other cryptocurrencies, the blockchain used for the Orbs Network is susceptible to mining attacks, including but not limited to double-spend attacks, majority mining power attacks, “Selfish-mining” attacks or race condition attacks and any successful attacks present a risk to the Orbs Network, expected proper execution and sequencing of transactions in Orbs Tokens, and expected proper execution and sequencing of contract computations. Despite the efforts of participants in the Orbs Network, including Validators and Guardians, known or novel mining attacks may be successful.
● if the Orbs Network is rapidly adopted, the demand for Orbs Tokens could rise dramatically and at a pace that exceeds the rate with which new Orbs Tokens are released from reserves or otherwise become available for use. Under such a scenario, the entire Orbs Network could become destabilized, due to the increased cost of running distributed applications. In turn, this could dampen interest in the Orbs Network and Orbs Tokens. Instability in the demand for Orbs Tokens may lead to a negative change of the economical parameters of an Orbs Token-based business which could result in the business being unable to continue to operate economically or to cease operation.
● if the Orbs Network is rapidly adopted, the demand for transaction processing and distributed application computations could rise dramatically and at a pace that exceeds the rate with which Validators can bring online additional computing power. Under such a scenario, the entire Orbs Network could become destabilized, due to the increased cost of running distributed applications. In turn, this could dampen interest in the Orbs Network and the Orbs Tokens. Insufficiency of computational resources and an associated rise in the price of Orbs Tokens could result in businesses being unable to acquire scarce computational resources to run their applications.
● It is possible that alternative which utilize the same open-source source code and open source protocol underlying the Orbs Network could be established. The Orbs Network may compete with these alternative networks, which could potentially negatively impact the Orbs Network and the Orbs Tokens; and
● the Orbs Network could be impacted in whole or in part by one or more regulatory or governmental inquiries or actions, which could impede, limit or restrict the use or transfer of Orbs Tokens or otherwise result in the complete or partial loss in value of Orbs Tokens.
You hereby expressly acknowledge and agree that: (i) you are accepting and interacting with the Orbs Network and any Orbs Tokens at your sole risk and expense; (ii) you have an adequate understanding of the risks, usage and intricacies of cryptographic tokens such as the Orbs Tokens and blockchain-based software such as the Orbs Network, including the risks set forth above; (iii) Orbs shall have no responsibility or liability for the loss, transfer, misappropriation, theft, use or misuse of any Orbs Tokens, including as utilized in connection with the Orbs Network, or any financial or physical harm or loss related thereto, and you hereby irrevocably waive any and all rights and claims with respect thereto and claims with respect thereto, (iv) you will comply with any and all applicable rules and laws regarding your use of Orbs Tokens, including in connection with the Orbs Network and (vi) Orbs does not endorse or recommend the use of any software or hardware wallet services and/or market exchanges (including any over-the-counter market) in connection with any storage, transfer or other transaction related to Orbs Tokens, all of which may be used at your sole risk and expense.

6. Contacting us

In order to contact us with respect to the App, please email us at: [hello@orbs.com]. Please see Section 3 for additional information about registering to the App.

7. Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and are committed to protect the information you share with us. We believe that you have a right to know our practices regarding the information we use or collect when you connect to, access or use the App. Our policy and practices and the type of information used are described in our Privacy Policy available on your device explorer at [Orbs POS Wallet - About - Privacy Policy], which is incorporated herein by reference. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time and such changes shall be effective as set forth in the Privacy Policy. You agree that Orbs and other participants on the Orbs Network may use personal information that you provide or make available in accordance with the Privacy Policy. If you intend to connect to, access or use the App you must first read and agree to the Privacy Policy.

8. Nature of Agreement and Termination

These Terms of Use represent a binding agreement between you and Orbs. These Terms of use shall remain in effect until such time as you discontinue your use of the App or until such time as the operations of the App, the Services or the Orbs Network are discontinued in accordance with Section 21 or any other applicable terms and conditions that may be in effect.
The Services being provided by the App allow you to utilize the Beta version of an architecture that is designed to provide you with the ability to manage your holdings in Orbs Tokens and participate in the Orbs Proof-of-Stake Ecosystem. Your use of the App allows you to take certain actions relating to the Orbs Network. By using the App, you acknowledge and agree that all such actions are subject to the terms and conditions set forth herein and in the Terms of Use of the Orbs Network, available at: https://github.com/orbs-network/orbs-network-go/blob/master/NETWORK-TOU.md, or such other applicable terms and conditions as may be in effect from time to time.
You agree that these Terms of Use, including the ability of Orbs and other third parties to use your personal information in accordance with our Privacy Policy, will continue for as long as these Terms of Use remain in place. You further acknowledge and agree that the provisions of these Terms that, by their nature and content, must survive the termination of these Terms in order to achieve the fundamental purposes of these Terms shall so survive even in the event that you disconnect from the App, by removing the relevant permissions in your Underlying Account, deleting the App or deleting your Underlying Account. Without limiting the generality of the forgoing, the Intellectual Property, Disclaimers of Warranties, Limitation of Liability, Indemnification and General sections will survive the termination of the Terms.
In the event you terminate this agreement, your personal information held by Orbs, if any, may be deleted in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

9. License; Intellectual Property Rights

Orbs hereby grants to you, and you accept, a personal, nonexclusive, non-commercial, non-transferable, non-sublicensable and fully revocable limited license (i) to use the Beta version of the App by connecting the App with an Underlying Account that you own or control, solely for the limited purpose of using the App for your internal non-commercial use, and for no other purpose, strictly in accordance with the Terms and applicable law; and (ii) to use the App and the Content provided in the App in accordance with the terms contained in these Terms.
The App, the Content and Orbs’ proprietary assets and any and all intellectual property rights pertaining thereto, including, but not limited to, inventions, patents and patent applications, trademarks, trade names, service marks, copyrightable materials, designs (including the “look and feel” of the App) specifications, domain names and trade secrets, whether or not registered or capable of being registered (excluding the User Generated Content, as defined below) (collectively, “Intellectual Property”), are owned by and/or licensed to Orbs and are protected by applicable copyright and other intellectual property laws and international conventions and treaties. All rights not expressly granted to you hereunder are reserved by Orbs and its licensors. These Terms do not convey to you an interest in or to Orbs Intellectual Property but only a limited revocable right of use in accordance with the Terms. Nothing in the Terms constitutes a waiver of Orbs’ Intellectual Property under any law.
To the extent you provide any feedback, comments or suggestions to Orbs in connection with this Beta version App (“Feedback”), Orbs shall have an exclusive, royalty-free, fully paid up, worldwide, perpetual and irrevocable license to incorporate the Feedback into any Orbs current or future products, technologies or services and use same for any purpose all without further compensation to you and without your approval. You agree that all such Feedback shall be deemed to be non-confidential. Furthermore, you warrant that your Feedback is not subject to any license terms that would purport to require Orbs to comply with any additional obligations with respect to any Orbs current or future products, technologies or services that incorporate any Feedback.

10. Trademarks and Trade Names

“Orbs ”, Orbs’ marks and logos and all other proprietary identifiers used by Orbs in connection with the App (“Orbs Trademarks”) are all trademarks and/or trade names of Orbs, whether or not registered. All other trademarks, service marks, trade names and logos which may appear on the App belong to their respective owners (“Third Party Marks”). No right, license, or interest to Orbs Trademarks and the Third Party Marks is granted hereunder, and you agree that no such right, license, or interest may be asserted by you with respect thereto and therefore you will avoid using any of those marks, except as permitted herein.

11. Changes to the App

The version of the App you are agreeing to use is a Beta version and may be subject to significant changes or updates. Orbs reserves complete and sole discretion with respect to the operation of the App and the Services and reserves the right to modify, correct, amend, enhance, improve, make any other changes to, or discontinue, temporarily or permanently the App, any Services or any part thereof, without notice, at any time. You hereby acknowledge that the Content and services provided via this App may be changed, extended in terms of content and form or removed at any time without any notice to you. You agree that Orbs shall not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension, or discontinuance of this App, the Services or the Content included therein. In addition, Orbs may at its sole discretion and without prior notice, create limits on usage and storage with respect to the App or the Services.

12. User Generated Content

The App may allow you to upload, post, publish and make available to other Users your own copyrightable materials, or references thereto (the “User Generated Content”). Please be sure that while you use the App you respect the proprietary rights including any intellectual property and privacy rights of third parties who have any rights with respect to the User Generated Content you uploaded to the App. Orbs will not bear any liability for any loss, damage, cost or expense that you may suffer or incur as a result of or in connection with uploading any User Generated Content. You hereby acknowledge and agree that the User Generated Content is non-confidential.
You understand and agree that you are solely responsible for your User Generated Content and the consequences of registering, sending, posting, publishing such User Generated Content, on the App, in any way. You represent and warrant that you are the rightful owner of the User Generated Content you upload to or register through the App or that you have (and will continue to have) all the necessary licenses, rights, consents, and permissions from the rightful owners of such User Generated Content and that such User Generated Content does not infringe any third party's intellectual property rights or other rights (including without limitation, any privacy rights, publicity rights, copyrights, or any other intellectual property rights). It is your responsibility to obtain any and all consents required under any applicable laws, regarding the posting of any personal information of others which is part of the User Generated Content, and to adhere to any applicable laws regarding such information.
Although Orbs has no obligation to screen, edit or monitor any of the User Generated Content, Orbs explicitly reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to remove or edit, without giving any prior notice, any User Generated Content available on the App at any time and for any reason, and you are solely responsible for creating backup copies of and replacing any User Generated Content you post on the App at your sole expense.
When you register or upload, post, publish or make available any User Generated Content on the App, you grant Orbs , as well as any other participant in the Orbs Network, including, without limitation, validator nodes, a perpetual, non-exclusive, royalty-free, and worldwide license to publicly display, communicate, distribute, host, publicly perform, publish, reproduce, make modifications or derivatives works (solely for the purpose of better showcasing your User Generated Content) store and to use such User Generated Content, in connection with the use and operation of the App. When you register, upload, post, publish or make available any User Generated Content to other Users on the App, you grant to such other Users a non-exclusive and royalty-free license, to access and view your User Generated Content. Please note that Orbs does not monitor or control what other Users do with your User Generated Content.
ORBS TAKES NO RESPONSIBILITY AND ASSUMES NO LIABILITY FOR ANY USER GENERATED CONTENT REGISTERED, UPLOADED, POSTED, PUBLISHED OR MADE AVAILABLE BY YOU OR ANY OTHER USER ON THE APP, OR FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE THERETO, NOR IS ORBS LIABLE FOR ANY MISTAKES, DEFAMATION, LIBEL, FALSEHOODS, OBSCENITIES OR PORNOGRAPHY YOU OR ANY OTHER USERS MAY ENCOUNTER. ORBS MAY AT ITS SOLE DISCRETION BLOCK ANY USERS OF THE APP AND/OR SERVICE FOR ANY VIOLATIONS OF THESE TERMS.

13. Use Restrictions

There are certain conducts that are strictly prohibited when using the App. Please read the following restrictions carefully. Failure to comply with any of the provisions set forth herein may also expose a User to civil and/or criminal liability.
You may not (and you may not permit any third party to) unless otherwise explicitly permitted under these Terms: (a) use the App, Services and/or Content for any illegal, immoral, unlawful and/or unauthorized purposes; (b) use the App, Services and/or Content for non-personal or commercial purposes without Orbs’ express prior written consent; (c) remove or disassociate, from the Content and/or the App any restrictions and signs indicating proprietary rights of Orbs or its licensors, including but not limited to any proprietary notices contained in such materials (such as ?,™, or ®), and you represent and warrant that you will abide by all applicable laws in this respect; (d) interfere with or violate Users' rights to privacy and other rights, or harvest or collect personally identifiable information about Users without their express consent, whether manually or with the use of any robot, spider, crawler, any search or retrieval application, or use other manual or automatic device, process or method to access the App and retrieve, index and/or data-mine information; (e) interfere with or disrupt the operation of the App or the servers or networks that host the App, or disobey any laws, regulations, requirements, procedures, or policies of such servers or networks; (f) falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with any person or entity, or express or imply that Orbs endorses you, your app, your business or any statement you make, or present false or inaccurate information about the App; (g) take any action that imposes, or may impose, an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on our platform infrastructure, as determined by us; (h) bypass any measures we may use to prevent or restrict access to the App; (i) copy, modify, alter, adapt, replicate, make available, translate, port, reverse engineer, decompile, or disassemble any portion of the Content made available by Orbs on or through the App, or publicly display, reproduce, create derivative works from, perform, distribute, or otherwise use such Content; (j) copy, distribute, display, execute publicly, make available to the public, reduce to human readable form, decompile, disassemble, adapt, sublicense, make any commercial use, sell, rent, transfer, lend, process, compile, reverse engineer, combine with other software, translate, modify or create derivative works of any material that is subject to Orbs’ proprietary rights, including Orbs’ Intellectual Property (as such term is defined above), in any way or by any means, unless expressly permitted in the Terms and/or under any applicable laws which expressly permits such actions; (k) make any use of the Content on any other App or networked computer environment for any purpose, without Orbs’ prior written consent; (l) create a browser or border environment around Orbs Content (no frames or inline linking is allowed); (m) sell, license, or exploit for any commercial purposes any use of or access to the App, Services and/or Content; (n) frame or mirror any part of the App without Orbs’ prior express written authorization; (o) create a database by systematically downloading and storing all or any of the Content from the App; (p) transmit or otherwise make available in connection with the App any virus, worm, Trojan Horse, time bomb, web bug, spyware, or any other computer code, file, or program that may or is intended to damage or hijack the operation of any hardware, software, or telecommunications equipment, or any other actually or potentially harmful, disruptive, or invasive code or component; (q) use the App if you are a citizen, resident or otherwise located in a country or region subject to comprehensive sections, including, but not limited to, the Crimean region of Ukraine, Cuba, Iran, Lebanon, North Korea, Sudan and Syria; (r) without derogating from the generality of any other provision of these Terms of Use, use the App for any type of activity associated with money laundering or terror financing, or to violate any provision of the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act of 1977, as amended, the UK Bribery Act (2010), Sections 290-297 of the Israeli Penal Law 1977 (Bribery Transactions), the Israeli Prohibition on Money Laundering Law, 2000, or any other applicable anti-corruption or anti bribery legislation, or use the App if you are subject to any investigation by, or has received a request for information from any governmental body relating to corruption or bribery under any statute; (s) use the App if you are a resident or citizen of any geographic area in which governmental authorities have indicated that the purchase or sale of digital assets such as the Orbs Tokens may be prohibited by applicable law, decree, regulation, treaty or administrative act; (t) use the App for any purpose for which the App is not intended; (u) infringe and/or violate any of the Terms; (v) register, post or upload any User Generated Content containing content which is unlawful for you to possess, post or upload in the country in which you are resident, or which it would be unlawful for Orbs to use or possess in connection with the App (including but not limited to any content which is defamatory, libelous, pornographic, indecent, harassing, threatening, abusive or fraudulent); and/or (w) register, post or upload any User Generated Content which include any unsolicited promotions, advertising, contests or raffles.

14. Usage Rules

Since you are connecting the App from your Underlying Account with a third party platform, service provider or distributor, such as Samsung (each, a “Platform Provider”), your use of the App may also be governed by usage rules which the Platform Provider may have established and which relate to your use of the App (“Usage Rules”). It is your responsibility to determine what Usages Rules are applicable to your use of the App. You undertake to comply with all the applicable Platform Provider's Usage Rules and the Usage Rules applicable to your use of the App are incorporated herein by reference. In the event of a conflict between the Terms and the terms of any applicable Usage Rules, which relates solely to the Platform Provider's representations, warranties, restrictions on use of the App, obligations, limitation of liability (to the extent applicable to the Platform Provider) and/or other provisions that impose any responsibility on the Platform Provider, the terms of the applicable Platform Provider's Usage Rules shall prevail. You represent that you are not prohibited by any applicable laws or Usage Rules from connecting the App to your Underlying Account and/or using the App. Any connecting of the App to an Underlying Account and/or use of the App by anyone prohibited by any applicable laws or Usage Rules from connecting the App to an Underlying Account and/or using the App is expressly prohibited."
    </string>
    <string name="text_terms_3" translatable="false">"
15. Misconduct and Copyright Agent

We care for your safety. If you believe a User acted inappropriately including (but not limited to) offensive, violent or sexually inappropriate behavior, please report immediately such person to the appropriate authorities and to our misconduct agent at [hello@orbs.com]. Orbs may at its sole discretion take any action including but not limited to blocking such User.
Orbs respects the intellectual property rights of others. If you believe that your work has been registered to the App or copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide the following information in writing to Orbs’ copyright agent: (i) a physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright; (ii) a description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed; (iii) a description of the material that you claim to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information sufficient to permit Orbs to locate the material; (iv) information so that Orbs can contact you, such as address, telephone number and e-mail address; (v) a statement that you believe in good faith that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and (vi) a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and, under penalty of perjury, that you are the copyright owner or are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of a copyright that is allegedly infringed. Orbs’ copyright agent can be reached [hello@orbs.com]
Orbs has the sole discretion to restrict and/or terminate access to the App to Users who are deemed to be repeat infringers of third party's copyright works or Users who acted inappropriately as specified above.

16. Third Party Components and Licenses

The App may use or include third party software, files and components that are subject to open source and third party license terms, such as Samsung or another Platform Provider, including, but not limited to, the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet (collectively, “Third Party Components”). The Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet may in turn incorporate additional Third Party Components. Your right to use such Third Party Components as part of, or in connection with, the App is subject to any applicable acknowledgements and license terms accompanying such Third Party Components, contained therein or related thereto. If there is a conflict between the licensing terms of such Third Party Components and these Terms, the licensing terms of the Third Party Components shall prevail in connection with the related Third Party Components. All Third Party Components are copyrighted by their respective authors. Such Third Party Components are provided on an “AS IS” basis without any warranty of any kind and shall be subject to any and all limitations and conditions required by such third parties. Under no circumstances shall the App or any portion thereof (except for the Third Party Components contained therein) be deemed to be “open source” or “publicly available” software.
Any Third Party Components licensed under open source licenses which may be linked to, interacted with, or used in connection with the App are done so pursuant to each individual open source component license and subject to the disclaimers and limitations on liability set forth in each open source component license.
As the App, as currently provided, is a Beta version, it is possible that additional Third Party Components may be incorporated that are not being used in the App on the date hereof. For the avoidance of doubt, the foregoing provisions shall applicable to all such Third Party Components.

17. Disclaimer of Warranties

TO THE FULLEST EXTENT LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE, THE APP AND SERVICES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY CONTENT, DATA AND INFORMATION, ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” , “WITH ALL FAULTS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS, AND ORBS, INCLUDING ITS VENDORS, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AFFILIATES, SUBSIDIARIES, LICENSORS, AGENTS AND SUPPLIERS (“ORBS REPRESENTATIVES”) DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO WARRANTIES OF TITLE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF USE, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
THE APP AND OR THE SERVICE IS INTENDED FOR INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY. WE DO NOT WARRANT (I) THAT THE APP OR THE SERVICE IS OR WILL BE SECURE, TIMELY, ACCURATE, COMPLETE, UNINTERRUPTED, WITHOUT ERRORS, OR FREE OF VIRUSES, DEFECTS, WORMS, OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS OR OTHER PROGRAM LIMITATIONS, (II) THAT THE APP AND/OR THE SERVICE WILL OPERATE AND/OR BE AVAILABLE AT ALL TIMES WITHOUT DISRUPTION OR INTERRUPTION, (III) THAT ORBS WILL CORRECT ANY ERRORS OR DEFECTS IN THE APP AND/OR THE SERVICE, (IV) AND/OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATION REGARDING THE USE, INABILITY TO USE OR OPERATE, OR THE RESULTS OF THE USE OF THE APP AND/OR THE SERVICE AND/OR CONTENT AVAILABLE THEREON OR THROUGH THE APP AND/OR THE SERVICE (INCLUDING THAT THE RESULTS OF USING THE APP AND/OR THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS).  ORBS HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS WITH REGARD TO THE USE OF THE APP AND/OR THE SERVICES AND/OR USER GENERATED CONTENT, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE AVAILABILITY, RELIABILITY OR THE QUALITY OF THE APP AND/OR THE SERVICE, AND IS NOT AND SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY ERROR, FAULT OR MISTAKE RELATED TO ANY CONTENT AND INFORMATION AND/OR USER GENERATED CONTENT DISPLAYED WITHIN THE APP. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE AND HAVE NO LIABILITY FOR ANY ITEM OR SERVICE PROVIDED BY ANY PERSON OR ENTITY OTHER THAN ORBS. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY CONSEQUENCES TO YOU OR OTHERS THAT MAY RESULT FROM TECHNICAL PROBLEMS (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION IN CONNECTION WITH THE INTERNET SUCH AS SLOW CONNECTIONS, TRAFFIC CONGESTION, OVERLOAD OF SERVERS, DELAYS OR INTERRUPTIONS) OR ANY TELECOMMUNICATIONS OR INTERNET PROVIDERS.
YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT THE APP IS A BETA VERSION OF AN ARCHITECTURE THAT UTILIZES NEWLY DEVELOPED BLOCKCHAIN TECHNOLOGY AND IS SUBJECT TO SIGNIFICANT RISKS ASSOCIATED WITH SUCH TECHNOLOGY AND WITH BETA APPLICATIONS IN GENERAL.
YOU AGREE THAT USE OF THE APP, THE SERVICES, THE USER GENERATED CONTENT AND/OR THE CONTENT IS ENTIRELY AT YOUR OWN RISK. WITHOUT LIMITING THE GENERALITY OF ANY OTHER PROVISION OF THE TERMS, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ASSUME FULL RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR USE OF THE APP AND THE ORBS POS WALLET FOR MOBILE. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT ANY INFORMATION YOU SEND OR RECEIVE DURING YOUR USE OF THE APP, THE ORBS NETWORK AND THE ORBS POS WALLET FOR MOBILE MAY NOT BE SECURE AND MAY BE INTERCEPTED OR LATER ACQUIRED BY UNAUTHORIZED PARTIES. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE APP, THE ORBS NETWORK AND THE ORBS POS WALLET FOR MOBILE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. RECOGNIZING SUCH, YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT, TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, NEITHER ORBS NOR ITS SUPPLIERS OR LICENSORS WILL BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE, EXEMPLARY OR OTHER DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, USE, DATA OR OTHER TANGIBLE OR INTANGIBLE LOSSES OR ANY OTHER DAMAGES BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR ANY OTHER THEORY (EVEN IF ORBS HAD BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES), RESULTING FROM THE APP OR ANY SERVICE; THE USE OR THE INABILITY TO USE THE APP OR THE SERVICE; UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR ALTERATION OF YOUR TRANSMISSIONS OR DATA; STATEMENTS OR CONDUCT OF ANY THIRD PARTY ON THE APP OR THE SERVICE; ANY ACTIONS WE TAKE OR FAIL TO TAKE AS A RESULT OF COMMUNICATIONS YOU SEND TO US; HUMAN ERRORS; TECHNICAL MALFUNCTIONS; FAILURES, INCLUDING PUBLIC UTILITY OR TELEPHONE OUTAGES; OMISSIONS, INTERRUPTIONS, LATENCY, DELETIONS OR DEFECTS OF ANY DEVICE OR NETWORK, PROVIDERS, OR SOFTWARE (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THOSE THAT DO NOT PERMIT PARTICIPATION IN THE SERVICE); ANY INJURY OR DAMAGE TO COMPUTER EQUIPMENT; INABILITY TO FULLY ACCESS THE APP OR THE SERVICE OR ANY OTHER WEBSITE; THEFT, TAMPERING, DESTRUCTION, OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO CONTENT OF ANY KIND; DATA THAT IS PROCESSED LATE OR INCORRECTLY OR IS INCOMPLETE OR LOST; TYPOGRAPHICAL, PRINTING OR OTHER ERRORS, OR ANY COMBINATION THEREOF; OR ANY OTHER MATTER RELATING TO THE APP OR THE SERVICE.
INASMUCH AS SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSIONS OR LIMITATIONS AS SET FORTH HEREIN, THE FULL EXTENT OF THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS AND LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY.

18. Limitation of Liability

TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE, IN NO EVENT SHALL ORBS, INCLUDING ORBS REPRESENTATIVES, BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, EXEMPLARY, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, UNDER ANY LEGAL THEORY (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, TORT OR STRICT LIABILITY) (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOSS OF GOODWILL, PROFITS OR DATA AND BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) ARISING HEREUNDER, RESULTING FROM OR ARISING OUT OF THE APP AND/OR THE SERVICES AND/OR THE CONTENT AND/OR USER GENERATED CONTENT, YOUR USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE APP AND/OR THE SERVICES AND/OR THE CONTENT AND/OR THE FAILURE OF THE APP TO PERFORM AS DESCRIBED OR EXPECTED, OR FROM THE PERFORMANCE OR FAILURE OF ORBS TO PERFORM UNDER THESE TERMS, ANY OTHER ACT OR OMISSION OF ORBS BY ANY OTHER CAUSE WHATSOEVER; OR BASED UPON BREACH OF WARRANTY, GUARANTEE OR CONDITION, BREACH OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, REGARDLESS OF WHETHER ORBS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
IN ANY CASE, WITHOUT LIMITING THE GENERALITY OF THE FOREGOING AND TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE, ORBS’ TOTAL AGGREGATE LIABILITY FOR ALL DAMAGES OR LOSSES WHATSOEVER ARISING HEREUNDER OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE APP AND/OR THE SERVICE OR THE CONTENT SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE AMOUNT ACTUALLY PAID BY YOU, IF ANY, TO ORBS FOR USE OF THE APP AND/OR SERVICE OR $US10.00, WHICHEVER IS GREATER. INASMUCH AS SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSIONS OR LIMITATIONS AS SET FORTH HEREIN, THE FULL EXTENT OF THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS AND LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY.

19. Indemnification

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Orbs, including the Orbs Representatives, from and against any and all claims, damages, obligations, losses, liabilities, costs, debts, and expenses (including but not limited to attorney's fees) arising from: (i) your use, misuse of, inability to use and/or activities in connection with the App, Services and/or Content; (ii) your violation of any of these Terms; (iii) your violation of any third party rights, including without limitation any intellectual property rights or privacy right of such third party with respect to your use of the App; (iv) any damage of any sort, whether direct, indirect, special or consequential, you may cause to any third party with relation to the App, and/or the Content; (v) the User Generated Content you uploaded to the App; and/or (vi) Orbs’ registration, publication, distribution or use of such User Generated Content you uploaded to the App. It is hereby clarified that this defense and indemnification obligation will survive these Terms.

Without derogating from the foregoing, we reserve the right to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter which is subject to indemnification by you, which will not excuse your indemnity obligations hereunder and in which event you will fully cooperate with us in asserting any available defense. You agree not to settle any matter subject to an indemnification by you without first obtaining our prior express written approval.

20. Amendments to the Terms

Orbs may, at its sole discretion, change the Terms from time to time, including any other policies incorporated thereto, so please re-visit this page frequently. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, due to the nature of the App, which is currently being provided in a Beta version, such changes may occur in connection with changes or updates to the App. In case of any material change, we will make reasonable efforts to post a clear notice on the introductory page of the App on the Samsung Galaxy Store regarding such change. Such material changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided. Otherwise, all other changes to these Terms are effective as of the stated “Last Revised” date and your continued use of the App on or after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes. In the event that the Terms should be amended to comply with any legal requirements, the amendments may take effect immediately, or as required by the law and without any prior notice.

21. Termination of the App's Operation

At any time, Orbs may discontinue your use of the App in its sole discretion with or without any reason or prior notice, in addition to any other remedies that may be available to Orbs under any applicable law.
Additionally, Orbs may at any time, at its sole discretion, cease the operation of the App or any part thereof, temporarily or permanently, without giving any prior notice. You agree and acknowledge that Orbs does not assume any responsibility with respect to, or in connection with the termination of the App's operation and loss of any data. The provisions of these Terms that, by their nature and content, must survive the termination of these Terms in order to achieve the fundamental purposes of these Terms shall so survive. Without limiting the generality of the forgoing, the Intellectual Property, Disclaimers of Warranties, Limitation of Liability, Indemnification and General sections will survive the termination of the Terms.

22. Minors

To use the App you must be over the age of eighteen (18). We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that minors under the age of eighteen (18) are not using the App. In the event that it comes to our knowledge that a person under the age of eighteen (18) is using the App, we will prohibit and block such User from accessing the App and will make all efforts to promptly delete any Personal Information (as such term is defined in our Privacy Policy) with regard to such User.

23. General

(a) These Terms constitute the entire terms and conditions between you and Orbs relating to the subject matter herein and supersedes any and all prior or contemporaneous written or oral agreements or understandings between you and Orbs, (b) any claim relating to the App and/or the use of the App and/or the Content contained therein will be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the State of Israel without reference to its conflict-of-laws principles, (c) any dispute arising out of or related to the App will be brought in, and you hereby consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue of, the competent courts of the Tel-Aviv-Jaffa District, Israel, provided, however, that nothing herein shall be deemed to preclude Orbs from bringing any suit, enforcing any right or taking other legal action in your local jurisdiction. You agree to waive all defenses of lack of personal jurisdiction and forum non-convenience and agree that process may be served in a manner authorized by applicable law or court rule. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Orbs may seek injunctive relief in any court of competent jurisdiction anywhere on the world, (d) these Terms do not, and shall not be construed to create any relationship, partnership, joint venture, employer-employee, agency, or franchisor-franchisee relationship between the parties hereto, (e) no waiver by either party of any breach or default hereunder will be deemed to be a waiver of any preceding or subsequent breach or default. Any heading, caption or section title contained herein is inserted only as a matter of convenience, and in no way defines or explains any section or provision hereof, (f) YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT ANY CAUSE OF ACTION THAT YOU MAY HAVE ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE APP AND/OR THE SERVICE MUST BE FILED WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER SUCH CLAIM AROSE. OTHERWISE, SUCH CAUSE OF ACTION IS PERMANENTLY BARRED, (g) if any provision hereof is adjudged by any court of competent jurisdiction to be unenforceable, that provision shall be limited or eliminated to the minimum extent necessary so that these Terms shall otherwise remain in full force and effect while most nearly adhering to the intent expressed herein, (h) you may not assign or transfer these Terms (including all rights and obligations hereunder) without our prior written consent and any attempt to do so in violation of the foregoing shall be void. We may assign or transfer these Terms without restriction or notification, (i) no amendment hereof will be binding unless in writing and signed by Orbs, and (j) the parties agree that all correspondence relating to these Terms shall be written in the English language.

24. Information, questions or notification of errors:

If you have any questions (or comments) concerning the Terms, you are most welcome to send us an e-mail to the following address and we will make an effort to reply within a reasonable timeframe : hello@orbs.com.

        "</string>

    <string name="text_policy_1" translatable="false">"Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile Privacy Policy

Last Revised: January 31, 2020

Orbs Ltd. and its affiliates (“Orbs”, “we” or “us”) respect the privacy of users (“User” or “you”) of the My Orbs Wallet application (the “App”) and available and related services and are committed to protecting the personal information that their Users share with us. We believe that you have a right to know our practices regarding the information we may collect and use when you visit and/or use our Site.
Capitalized terms which are not defined herein, shall have the meaning ascribed to them in our Terms of Use at [About - Terms of Use] (“TOU”), into which this Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference.
This Privacy Policy and the ToU into which this Privacy Policy is incorporated relate solely to the App and its use. Use of the Orbs decentralized network platform and any activity thereon is subject to the Orbs Network Terms of Use which are available at [https://www.orbs.com/terms-of-use/].

1. Your Consent (PLEASE READ CAREFULLY!)

BY ENTERING, CONNECTING TO, ACCESSING OR USING THE APP, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY (THE “PRIVACY POLICY”), INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION, USE AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR USE THE APP.
FOR THE AVOIDANCE OF DOUBT, YOU HEREBY CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, PROCESSING, TRANSFER AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. YOU ALSO ACKNOWLEDGE AND CONFIRM THAT YOU ARE NOT REQUIRED TO PROVIDE US WITH ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION AND THAT SUCH INFORMATION IS VOLUNTARILY PROVIDED TO US.

2. Which information we may collect on our Users?

We may collect two types of data and information from our Users:
  a. Non-identifiable and anonymous information (“Non-personal Information”). We are not aware of the identity of the User from whom we have collected the Non-personal Information. Non-Personal Information is any unconcealed information which does not enable identification of an individual User, and which is available to us while such User downloads, enters into and/or uses the App. Non-personal Information which may be gathered consists of technical information, and behavioral information, and may contain, among other things, the activity of the User on the App, type of operating system, User's transaction types or searches on the App, the device you use to access your account, including the hardware model, operating system and version type and version of browser, keyboard language, screen resolution, etc. Non-Personal Information which may be collected, will be collected in an aggregated form in order to allow us to evaluate and improve the performance of the App.
  b. Personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”). This information may identify an individual or may be of a private and/or sensitive nature. Orbs does not collect or store any of your Personal Information. However, the App is required to access and use certain of your Personal Information in order to allow you to utilize the functionality of the App to manage your holdings of Orbs Tokens and participate in the Orbs Proof-of-Stake Ecosystem.
Certain of the Personal Information required for the App’s functionality is stored on your device, in the local storage folder associated with the App. Such Personal Information is loaded to your local storage folder automatically when you download the App and associate it with your Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet account. This category of Personal Information may include, inter alia:
● Wallet addresses on the Ethereum blockchain in which you hold your Orbs Tokens, which you may manually enter once the App is downloaded, in order to monitor such wallet addresses, without the ability to engage in any transactions (“Read Only Wallet Address”).
● Wallet addresses on the Ethereum blockchain in which you hold your Orbs Tokens that are associated with your Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet account, which will be automatically saved in the App’s designated storage folder on your device (“Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile Address”).
● A name for your Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile that you will select and input to the App.
● Your preferred setting for “gas” fees to allow for processing on the Ethereum blockchain of any transaction that you initiate through the App.
● A “Seedhash” generated by your Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet account.
● A wallet address on the Ethereum blockchain in which you hold your Orbs Tokens, which you will manually enter once the App is downloaded.
The App may also access and use information, including certain information that may qualify as Personal Information, that has been stored on a public blockchain network like the Ethereum Blockchain or the Orbs Network. Such information will be accessed by the App from the applicable blockchain network in real-time when necessary for the functionality of the App, but will not be stored on your device or otherwise by Orbs. Such information may include:
● The balance of Orbs Tokens held in any Read Only Wallet Address or any Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile Address.
● The history of delegation to Guardians of the Orbs Tokens held in any Read Only Wallet Address or any Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile Address.
● The history of rewards distributed to any Read Only Wallet Address or any Orbs POS Wallet for Mobile Address as a result of participation in the Orbs Proof-of-Stake Ecosystem.
● Other transaction information effected by you or other participants in the Orbs Network or the Ethereum blockchain.
For the avoidance of doubt, any Non-Personal Information that may be connected or linked to any Personal Information shall be deemed as Personal Information as long as such connection or linkage exists.
We do not collect any Personal Information from you or related to you without your approval, which is obtained, inter alia, through your active acceptance to the TOU and the Privacy Policy.
Orbs does not store any of your Personal Information. Any Personal Information used by the App is stored on your own device or on a public blockchain network, as applicable.
Please note that third parties, such as Samsung or nodes and other participants in the Orbs Network or the Ethereum Blockchain, may collect, record and store certain Personal Information as a result of your use of the App, as described in further detail in Section 6.

3. How Do We Collect Information on Our Users?

There are a few methods that we may use:
a. We collect information through your entry and use of the App. In other words, when you download or are using the App we are aware of it and may gather, collect and store the information relating to such usage.
b. We collect information which you decide to provide us voluntarily. For example, we collect Personal Information and store such Personal Information on your device when you download the App and elect to enter a Read Only Wallet Address or link the App to the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet.
c. We utilize information which is stored on public blockchain networks like the Ethereum Blockchain and the Orbs Network. We may gather, collect and store such information either independently or through the help of our authorized third-party service providers as detailed below.

4. What are the Purposes of the Collection of Information?

Non-personal Information may be collected in order to:
● Use it for statistical and research purposes and for customization and improvement of our App and services;
● Enhance the User's experience while using the App;
● for business development purposes such as statistical and marketing analysis, systems testing, maintenance and development, customer surveys or to help us in any future dealings with you, for example by identifying your requirements and preference;
● to comply with any legal or regulatory requirements;
● to protect the safety and well being of yourself and/or other customers; and
● for all other purposes ancillary to any of the purposes stated above.
Personal Information is collected and used in order to:
● to permit you to utilize all functionality of the App, including monitoring your holdings of Orbs Tokens and participating in the Orbs Proof-of-Stake Ecosystem;
● for all other purposes ancillary to any of the purposes stated above.
"</string>
    <string name="text_policy_2" translatable="false">"
5. Sharing Information with Third Parties

Orbs will not share any Personal Information it may collect with any third party, other than in the following circumstances: (a) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce this Privacy Policy and/or the TOU, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to respond to claims that contact information (e.g. name, e-mail address, etc.) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; (e) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Orbs, its Users or the general public; (f) by virtue of undergoing any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of the assets of Orbs, so long as such acquirer maintains the same privacy terms hereunder; or (g) pursuant to your explicit approval prior to the disclosure.
Note, that we may collect, hold and/or manage Personal Information through Orbs' authorized third parties vendors of certain products or services (such as, hosting cloud services) or through  (including, as applicable, their affiliates) solely and limited to providing us with such requested services, and not for any other purposes. Such vendors may be located in a country that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction.
For avoidance of doubt, Orbs may use Non-personal Information and transfer and disclose it to third parties at its discretion.

6. Information Collected By Third Parties

The App is designed as a plug in/extension to the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet and connects to the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet in order to allow for its functionality, which includes taking actions on the Orbs Blockchain Network and the Ethereum Blockchain.
The Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet is a third-party application that is not under the control of Orbs and Orbs has no control over any actions or omissions of Samsung.
Samsung may, pursuant to the terms and conditions applicable to the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet and any other documents governing your use of Samsung’s services, including, without limitation, collect Non-Personal Information or Personal Information from you. You acknowledge and agree that Orbs has no control over, and no duty to take any action regarding, any collection of Non-Personal Information or Personal Information from you by Samsung.
You should review the terms of use, privacy policy and any other applicable terms of your device and the Samsung Blockchain Infrastructure or Ledger HW wallet, which are available through Samsung’s website, within your device or by such other medium as may be provided by Samsung from time to time.
The Orbs Network and Ethereum Blockchain are public blockchains that are each operated by a decentralized network of participants. In the case of the Orbs Network, such participants are known as Validators and Guardians and in the case of the Ethereum blockchain, such participants are validator nodes known as miners. If you engage in any transactions with respect to Orbs Tokens through the App, the results of such actions will be recorded by such decentralized networks of participants. Public block chains are distributed ledgers, intended to immutably record transactions across wide networks of computer systems. Many block chains are open to forensic analysis which can lead to deanonymization and the unintentional revelation of private financial information, especially when block chain data is combined with other data.
Because these blockchains are decentralized or third-party networks that are not controlled or operated by Orbs or its affiliates, we are not able to erase, modify, or alter Personal Information from such networks.

7. Deletion of Personal Information

In any event, if for any reason you (or any person) wish to delete your Personal Information, please uninstall the App from your device.  Upon uninstalling the App, all Personal Information stored in the designated local storage folder associated with the App on your device will be automatically deleted. Note that unless otherwise explicitly specified herein and/or unless you instruct us otherwise we may retain your Personal Information for as long as reasonably required for the purposes of which such Personal Information was collected, all as permitted under any applicable privacy laws.
Aggregated and/or anonymous information derived from your use of the Site may remain on our servers indefinitely. Deletion or modification of any information stored by Samsung is subject to Samsung’s privacy policy and any other applicable terms. As set forth in Section 6, we are unable to erase, modify or alter any information stored on the Ethereum Blockchain or the Orbs Network.

8. Minors

The App is intended for Users over the age of eighteen (18). Therefore, Orbs does not intend and does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under this age. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that minors under this age are not using the App.

9. Security

We take reasonable measures to maintain the security and integrity of the App and prevent unauthorized access to it or use thereof through generally accepted industry standard technologies and internal procedures. Any Personal Information used by Orbs is stored on your device, which we believe provides advanced strict security standards (both physical and logical), or on public blockchain networks that employ highly secure design and implementation using encryption and architectures mechanisms. Please note, however, that there are inherent risks in transmission of information over the Internet or other methods of electronic storage and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access or use will never occur. ORBS SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS, HACKING, OR OTHER SECURITY INTRUSIONS OR FAILURE TO STORE OR THE THEFT, DELETION, CORRUPTION, DESTRUCTION, DAMAGE, OR LOSS OF ANY DATA OR INFORMATION.

10. Third Party Service Providers

While providing the App we may use third party service providers, who may collect, store and/or process the information detailed herein. Orbs uses commercially reasonable efforts to engage with third parties that post a privacy policy governing their collection, processing and use of non-personal and personal information.

11. Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies.

When you access or use the App, we or our third party service providers may use industry-wide technologies such as “cookies” or other similar technologies which store certain information on your computer or device (“Cookies”), which will allow us to enable automatic activation of certain features and make your experience much more convenient and effortless. We or our authorized third party service providers may use both session cookies (which expire once you close the Site) and persistent cookies (which stay on your system until you delete them). It is easy to disable or delete Cookies. Most browsers will allow?you?to erase cookies from your computer's hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if?you?disable or erase cookies, your online experience may be limited. Cookies usually store only a Non-personal Information, such as the web pages you have visited, the duration of your browsing, etc. Orbs does not control such third party service providers.

12. International Data Transfer

In the course of your use of the App, information collected about you, including Personal Information,  may be transferred to affiliated entities of Orbs or Samsung, to other third party service providers or to participants in a public blockchain (as provided herein) across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. Please note that such information may be transferred to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to such transfer of information.

13. Changes to the Privacy Policy

The terms of this Privacy Policy will govern the use of the App and any information collected therein. Orbs reserves the right to change this policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently. We will provide notice of substantial changes of this policy on the introductory page of the App on the Samsung Galaxy Store. Such substantial changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided on the App. Otherwise, all other changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Revised” date and your continued use of the App after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes. In the event that the Terms should be amended to comply with any legal requirements, the amendments may take effect immediately, or as required by law and without any prior notice.

14. Questions and Complaints.

If you have any questions (or comments) concerning this Privacy Policy, you are most welcome to send us an email to the following address: [hello@orbs.com].
        "</string>
    <string name="open_source_license" translatable="false">"Apache License

Version 2.0, January 2004

http://www.apache.org/licenses/

TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION

1. Definitions.

\"License\" shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction, and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.

\"Licensor\" shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by the copyright owner that is granting the License.

\"Legal Entity\" shall mean the union of the acting entity and all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition, \"control\" means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.

\"You\" (or \"Your\") shall mean an individual or Legal Entity exercising permissions granted by this License.

\"Source\" form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications, including but not limited to software source code, documentation source, and configuration files.

\"Object\" form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical transformation or translation of a Source form, including but not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation, and conversions to other media types.

\"Work\" shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work (an example is provided in the Appendix below).

\"Derivative Works\" shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of, the Work and Derivative Works thereof.

\"Contribution\" shall mean any work of authorship, including the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, \"submitted\" means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems, and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise designated in writing by the copyright owner as \"Not a Contribution.\"

\"Contributor\" shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and subsequently incorporated within the Work.

2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of, publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.

3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable (except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made, use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work, where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s) with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You institute patent litigation against any entity (including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate as of the date such litigation is filed.

4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You meet the following conditions:

You must give any other recipients of the Work or Derivative Works a copy of this License; and
You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices stating that You changed the files; and
You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and attribution notices from the Source form of the Work, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works; and
If the Work includes a \"NOTICE\" text file as part of its distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or, within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed as modifying the License.

You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and may provide additional or different license terms and conditions for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use, reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with the conditions stated in this License.
5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise, any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of this License, without any additional terms or conditions. Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed with Licensor regarding such Contributions.

6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor, except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.

7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each Contributor provides its Contributions) on an \"AS IS\" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.

8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory, whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise, unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special, incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill, work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor has been advised of the possibility of such damages.

9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer, and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity, or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.

END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS

HOW TO APPLY THE APACHE LICENSE TO YOUR WORK
You should include a copy of the Apache License, typically in a file called LICENSE, in your work, and consider also including a NOTICE file.

To apply the Apache License to specific files in your work, attach the following boilerplate declaration, with the fields enclosed by brackets \"[]\" replaced with your own identifying information. (Don't include the brackets!) The text should be enclosed in the appropriate comment syntax for the file format. We also recommend that a file or class name and description of purpose be included on the same \"printed page\" as the copyright notice for easier identification within third-party archives.

Copyright [yyyy] [name of copyright owner]

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License\");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.

"</string>
</resources>